This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Damn!
Haven't the Demi's Lad sprays stopped yet?
At this rate, we'll be stuck
here with this caravan forever.
Chill out and have a drink.
They'll stop before you know it.
I don't know.
Looks like we're here.
Another one on me.
Mmm, yeah.
What's wrong?
Had enough, mister?
Will you be quiet?
I am trying to think here!
Whoa, sorry.
Take it easy, fella.
Oh, man.
Now what am I supposed to do?
Should I butt this guy in the
head and make a break for it?
No, no, I can't do that.
What am I thinking?
I'm a man of God, for God's sake.
One, two, three, four.
She really needs dancing lessons.
Oh?
All right, back to reality here.
What do I do?
What?
You don't have pudding?
A simple look around will tell you we
don't serve that kind of stuff here.
Sorry, Missy.
I just asked for pudding.
You don't need to be so rude.
Are you listening to me?
Hey, what's the problem?
Hey, Mr.
Priest, what a peasant surprise.
Ha, pleasant.
Well, what brings you here?
Don't tell me you guys are
traveling with this caravan.
Yeah, that's right. Meryl and Mr.
Vash are here with me. What?
Hey, do you mean Vash the Stampede here?
Oh, well, yeah. Do you
know him, too? Know him?
Hell, little lady, he's
the humanoid typhoon.
What's with the hand
next to my knight, buddy?
Sorry about that.
Hey, aren't God's little
creatures wonderful?
And so darn smart.
Oh, my.
I'm about to go down in flames.
Hey,
what are you doing don't you
realize that the rest of my fear is
riding on the outcome of this game
you trying to get me thrown out?
Oh, I give up what what's the matter?
Oh
I'll be damned
Thank you for buying
all of these for me, Mr.
Wolfwood I should be thanking you.
You saved my bacon, chess master!
I guess I'm good at chess.
My big brother used to make me
play chess with him all the time.
A big brother, huh?
Gee, that must be nice Any other siblings?
No, but there's ten brothers and sisters
uh-huh you're the youngest
aren't you yeah wow
how did you know that
sometimes the answers just
crash down from heaven
hey aren't you the dancing
girl from before I need
your help please don't let
Hold it. What's the matter?
Which way did she go? Is she in trouble?
Just answer the question.
Oh, all right.
All right.
Relax, mister You'll find
her hiding right behind me.
What the hell I?
Answered your question now.
I believe it's only fair
you answer mine there or not
This ain't got nothing to do with you.
Huh?
What's the matter with you?
That happened to be my can of pudding.
You wasted it.
You should never get between
people and their pudding.
But you are the one who
dropped them, you know.
Um, thank you very much for your help.
I have to go now.
I heard gunfire from over there.
Get all the guys together.
We can't let her escape.
There she is!
Gee, young lady, you're enormous.
Are you expecting sextuplets?
Isn't it lovely out today, honey?
Excruciatingly pleasant, honey.
I am really sorry about all this.
It's all right.
Just stay out of sight.
Did you see her?
No, nowhere!
She couldn't have gone too far.
Just find her!
Right!
How did this happen?
No matter what I do, I always seem
to get into trouble with this girl.
Hey!
Secondhand smoke is bad
for the baby, darling.
Oh, yeah, geez.
Sorry about that, honey.
It's been ages since Millie left to
go buy whatever she's looking for.
What on earth is keeping
that girl so long?
I'm really getting tired of waiting.
Huh?
Hey, mister, is it true that
you're Vash the Stampede?
I'm so sorry for causing you any trouble.
It's nice to be able
to lend a helping hand.
Since I'm already in this so deep, will
you at least tell me what's going on?
Actually, I'm...
Who did that?
Get away from Moore! What the?
Julius, stop shooting! Huh?
These people, help me!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Hey, you're not late. More.
Julius.
What's that all about?
Julius and I have been
friends since childhood.
But he's the son of the owner of
the big transportation company,
which passes through Demislat.
And, well, I'm just a simple dancing girl.
Yeah, but why are they after you?
It's Fondrique. What?
Do you mean Fondrique as
in the big city, Fondrique?
Fondrique City's transportation needs
have been left solely to my company,
to my caravan.
Unfortunately,
the security over there is so tight,
I can't even get in without a pass.
It's a very difficult situation.
So you're looking for your pass?
No,
I'm looking for my son,
although he's actually
not my real son My so
-called father just so
happens to be the mayor of
Fondrique And the caravan
needs me because I'm
the only pass they have
letting them into the city
So they're actually after you and not
her That's still no reason to run away
like you did Running away is not going
to solve anything But we do have a reason
I ran away the day I discovered
that my real father and the
man I thought was my father
were doing something despicable.
Sure,
Fondrique did use the caravan
to import cargo all right,
but their cargo wasn't always in boxes.
Now, come here.
We bought you human rights. We own you.
You have no choice.
Help me! Mother! Mother!
They treat people like
their personal property.
That's the way they're able
to get so rich. Horrible.
Well then, am I right in assuming that
she's supposed to be the new cargo?
That's exactly the reason
we had to run away.
We can't go on living like this!
Please
I need your help I need you to get
my Julius back from me Without him
all trade will stop completely It'll be
the end of this caravan We'll never survive
Twenty million double dollars That's my
price and it's not up for negotiation
Twenty million?
That is ludicrous!
Then find someone else to help you.
All right, it's a deal then!
I'll pay your price.
However, I need to ask you
for one other condition.
I just wanted to say thank you for helping
Mor get away from those men. Let's go.
So, where are you headed now?
Someplace where we can be free.
I hope you're not planning to go that way!
You'll be killed!
The caravan people are pretty familiar
with the land surrounding this area.
But I'm sure they wouldn't
dare follow us through there.
Even if it means the end of the caravan?
Oh.
If you leave, they lose
their contract with the city.
The caravan goes under,
and everybody dies.
Any caravan that's
willing to participate in
something like that should
not be allowed to survive.
I hope Fondry goes under, too.
I've heard enough.
People are gonna die because of you.
Now you listen to me.
It's all so easy for you to say
because you're running away from it
Say that after you watch them
die right in front of you
Would you be able to make your
escape over the bodies of the dead?
We've made up our minds to do this
and it's none of your business
That's true.
You're right
Mr. Priest!
However, the fewer sacrificed, the better.
Am I right?
The fewer sacrificed, the better.
Mr. Priest!
Your freedom or the lives of
the people in the caravan?
It's plain to see which is more important.
I'll choose for you.
If you do decide to leave,
somebody is going to die.
Well, can you do it?
Are you still able to just run away?
I'm waiting for you to show
me how determined you are.
I don't think leaving's a good idea.
Hey, I'm not kidding!
Thanks a lot.
I don't want your thanks.
I asked you an important question.
I have yet to receive an answer.
And I still think that
what you're doing is wrong.
That's true.
But we still want to thank you.
You're going with them.
Well.
I can't just ignore them.
Can I.
If you're doing it out of sympathy.
See, forget it.
It's not our problem, and there's
nothing you can do to help them.
I'm going because it's what
my big sister told me to do.
When people need help, if
I can, I have to help them.
Okay?
She does everything I can't,
like it's no big deal at all.
It's really irritating.
We really should be more careful.
If it gets up, you're going
to leave terrible scars.
You must go back, please.
There's no reason for you to put
yourself in danger by coming with us.
You know, anything can happen
no matter where you are.
Besides, they say journeys are social
scars that could affect your life.
You shouldn't joke
about a thing like that.
Huh?
You know, you're really funny, Miss...
My name is Millie Thompson.
what did that man ask
you to do it's nothing
nasty i hope hey why
don't you say anything
Look out!
Millie, are you alright?
It was a little hot, but I'm fine now.
I feel so powerless.
Maybe he wasn't my real
father, but I couldn't help it.
I loved him anyway.
That's why I want him to stop.
I don't want to live like this,
knowing that my success depends
on the suffering of others.
It's all so crazy my actions are making
everyone suffer and now
i'm dragging you into it.
Maybe the priest was right after all
but i'm fine really there they are.
When are you going to stop
this and say something?
All right then you talk
to me he wanted a kill.
A kill that's right and you accept it yes.
You're nothing but a despicable
outlaw just like i thought.
Very well if that's the case.
I have no choice but to execute
risk prevention procedure.
Would you mind at least explaining
why you decided to do this?
No, no, no!
Let them get away!
Ow! My back?
No!
Julius!
Run, Mar! Run!
I can't!
I can't leave you!
Mar!
Julius!
It's time for you to stop running.
Is that my father's order?
Actually, it's the entire
caravan's decision.
Ray, stop!
Stop it now!
You win.
I'll go back.
But you can't.
We've come this far.
You can't just go back now.
Millie's right.
You've got to listen to her.
Don't give up, Julius.
Come on.
It's time to go back.
Oh, Julius.
Ah! Mr. Priest!
Priest, I'm gonna pummel you!
More!
Lord, what the hell am I doing here?
Thank you so much!
I'm glad you came.
What made you change your mind?
I don't know.
Guess I was infected by your nosiness.
I think I actually caught it from Vash.
Well now, looking for a fight,
then you'd better expect no mercy!
Look, well if it isn't Vash the Stampede?
No way was he hired by
my father, please you.
Gotta help us, Vash, for
the future of the caravan.
Have you any idea what you're doing?
Yep.
Your God is my witness.
No!
But...
but you shot Julius.
It's all over.
Our pass is dead.
Hey, it was never part of
the agreement to kill him.
Your boss hired me to stop them.
He never mentioned their safety.
I've finished the job.
Now leave the money and get lost.
What did you say?
Don't do it, are you suicidal?
I think we made a big mistake here, guys.
We should never have gone to
someone like him for help.
He's just like they said he's
gonna kill us all as well.
Now he's really done it!
How could...
How could he do this?
How could you even think of doing
such a horrible, evil thing?
Millie.
Oh, Meryl.
Meryl!
They're gone.
I can't believe it.
He shot them both.
He shot them, Meryl.
I watched them both die!
You want to settle what we
started back in May City? Come on!
That was a realistic performance.
Pretty tough to kill when you're
shooting with rubber bullets.
Hey, don't fire those
so close. That stings.
I have a message from your father.
He says he's sorry for deceiving you,
and that even though it's no excuse,
he only did it because he was
protecting you and the caravan.
I understand.
Oh, and there's one other thing.
He asked me to tell you,
you're now free to go.
Father.
Julius!
I'm not sure how to thank you.
Don't thank me.
He's the one that deserves it.
Hey, you forgot this!
Now quickly, you've gotta
go before they spot you.
Momma.
From this point on, we're gonna go
on living without relying on anyone.
It'll be just the two of us.
Well, Millie, you take
care of yourself, okay?
And thus, your name is being spread
across the planet even as we speak.
Maybe this is what they call karma.
Oh, I don't think so.
She's a good girl, isn't she?
She's really good.
Yes, she is.
And you, my friend, are just like her.
What?
You mean he's really
left for good this time?
All of life's journeys come with
meetings and partings and reunions.
I guess that's true.
I've got things to do,
so I'll be going now.
Will I see you again?
I don't know.
And besides, whenever I look at you, I'm
reminded of everything I hate about myself.
You know, it hurts.
Nicholas D. Wolfwood.
I'll be darned.
All along, I thought there
had to be a sacrifice.
But there was another answer after all.
Vash the stampede.
The blue sky in the middle of the
sky, the wind is in the future.
The light of the day of
the sky, as you can see?
Thank you.
Thank you so much for watching.
No, no, no!
Deeper than darkness, Legato Blue
Summers, a man fascinated by death,
only spoke quietly.